changeyourlife.com 2001-06-19

# Self Improvement: Learn Online with Dreamlife Experts

|    
  
---  

**AN OVERVIEW**

Dreamlife is strongly committed to protecting your privacy. The Dreamlife Web site does not collect personal information about individuals except when knowingly provided by such individuals (or as otherwise described below). When you register and respond to any request at our site for personal information (for example, your name and e-mail address), we may, from time to time, disclose the information that you provide to third parties in order to provide you with information about relevant products and services. If you do not wish to receive e-mail or other correspondence related to Dreamlife or other promotions or products, simply indicate your preference when you are asked to provide the information. In addition, please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online (for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas), that information can be collected and used by Dreamlife and by others and may result in unsolicited messages. 

**COOKIES**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. We use 'cookie' technology in a limited way to help deliver advertisements, to identify unique browsers that visit us and to track usage throughout our site. Additionally, each time you visit any of our sites, our servers automatically collect information about which pages are visited and the domain name of visitors for purposes of research and analysis. All of this information is used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for traffic audits. In some instances, the information may be aggregated and sold to third parties.

In cases where you supply us with personal information as part of an online survey, you may receive a phone call from us for confirmation purposes or, when indicated, for an interview by a reporter. 

**IMPORTANT EXCEPTIONS**

Notwithstanding anything else in this privacy policy, Dreamlife may release account information when it believes that such release is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with law, (2) enforce or apply terms of any of our member agreements, or (3) protect the rights, property or safety of Dreamlife, other users, or others. 

**OUTSIDE PARTIES AND SITES**

Through Dreamlife you may be introduced to a variety of third-party vendors and sites. For example, you can review the products offered by the vendors included on our site. The privacy policies of these third parties are not under our control and may differ from ours. The use of any information that you may provide to any third party, or the use of "cookie" technology by any third party, will be governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site that you are visiting. In some cases these third parties may share the information that they collect about you with Dreamlife. If you have any doubts about the privacy of the information you are providing on another site, we recommend that you contact that site directly for more information and review their privacy policy. 

Our Web site uses a reputable third party to serve the advertisements that you see on the pages of our Web site. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices and [**opt-out**](http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm) procedures of our third party ad server, please [**click here**](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm). 

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by Dreamlife. If we find it necessary or desirable to change our privacy policy in the future, we will post changes as soon as they go into effect so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**LET US KNOW WHAT YOU THINK**

If you have any questions or comments about your privacy and Dreamlife, please let us know on our **Feedback** page.
